[Music]
uh my name is Julia and I'm currently an
operation strategy analyst on the GM
operations leadership
[Music]
team every project is a bit different so
there's no sense of it being kind of the
same thing every day uh I think every
day you get to challenge yourself and
learn something new it's really cool
because some of the projects we work on
actually have a big impact on like the
business and even as an intern uh and
now as a new grad I've worked on
projects and I've seen kind of the
impact that my work has
[Music]
done that that's my like favorite part
of my day is you know being able to use
the organization's data to kind of
actually drive insides and help uh make
key decisions within man life there's a
big emphasis in terms of just being able
to focus on your well-being while also
being productive at works
[Music]